In this example, we will see the semantics of a small piece of code which works
在这个例子中，我们将看到一小段代码的语义，它适用于这个
with this struct rect_t.
struct rect_t。
This struct represents a rectangle with four ints, left, bottom, right, and top.
这个结构表示一个包含四个整数的矩形，分别是左、下、右和上。
And here are some code which declares and uses the struct rect_t.
这里有一些声明和使用结构 rect_t 的代码。与
As always, we start execution at the beginning of main.
往常一样，我们从 main 的开头开始执行。
The first statement declares a variable of type rect_t called myRect.
第一条语句声明了一个名为 myRect 的 rect_t 类型的变量。
We will draw a box for this variable inside of main's frame and
我们将在主框架内为这个变量画一个方框
label it myRect.
并将其标记为 myRect。
However, unlike other boxes we have drawn, this box has four other boxes inside
但是，与我们绘制的其他方框不同，这个方框里面还有另外四个方框
of it, one for each field of the struct, left, bottom, right, and top.
，一个用于结构的每个字段，分别是左、下、右和上。
As we have not assigned any values to these fields,
由于我们没有为这些字段分配任何值，因此
these boxes are uninitialized so we have placed question marks in them.
这些框未初始化，因此我们在其中放置了问号。
The next line says myRect.left = -4.
下一行说 myrect.left = -4。
This is an assignment statement, so
这是一个赋值语句，所以
we must find the box named by the left hand side.
我们必须找到左边命名的方框。
The first part of this line names myRect, which is the entire large box.
这行的第一部分命名为 myRect，这是整个大方框。
However, it says .left, which names the box labelled left inside of myRect box.
但是，它显示的是.left，它命名了 myRect 框内标有左边的方框。
Remember that dot means inside of.
请记住，圆点的意思是里面。
So now we will put -4 into this box.
因此，现在我们将在此框中输入 -4。
The next line behaves similarly, except that we are putting 1
下一行的行为类似，唯一的不同是我们在
into the bottom box inside of the myRect box, and likewise for
myRect 框的底部方框中输入 1，同样用于
assigning 8 to the myRect.right, and assigning 6 to myRect.top.
将 8 分配给 myrect.right，将 6 分配给 myrect.top。
Now we are going to print some information about this rectangle.
现在我们要打印一些关于这个矩形的信息。
Again, myRect.left names the left box inside of the myRect.box.
再说一遍，myrect.left 命名了 myrect.box 内的左边方框。
So we will pass -4 to printf for the first %d.
因此，我们将第一个 %d 传递给 printf。对于
And we will pass 1 to printf for the second %d.
第二个 %d，我们将将 1 传递给 printf。
So we will print that bottom left = (-4, 1).
所以我们将打印左下角的 = (-4, 1)。
We will then do a similar thing for the top right.
然后我们将对右上角做类似的事情。
Now you have seen the semantics of declaring and using structs
现在你已经看到了声明和使用结构体的语义